<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="Create a Hello World Application">
   <taskGroup kind="set" name="Create a DaoJones Hello World Application" skip="false">
      <intro>
         In this tutorial, you will create a Java application accessing a Notes database using DaoJones and the local Notes client installation.
In the example, you will create a TODO item in your mail database. To practise the query language, you will search for the task in a second example.
      </intro>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Prepare local Notes client" skip="false">
         <intro>
            To access the database, you have to prepare your local Notes client.
         </intro>
         <param name="path" value="tasks/0_PrepareNotesClient.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Set up DaoJones project" skip="false">
         <intro>
            In this step, you will create the Java project and configure its Build Path to include the DaoJones runtime.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            Now you have a Java project containing the DaoJones runtime.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="tasks/1_SetupProject.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Configure DaoJones connections" skip="false">
         <intro>
            To access the database, you need to configure the connections within a configuration file. Then you have to read the configuration file within your application.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b>
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="tasks/2_Configure DaoJones connections.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Create Task bean" skip="false">
         <intro>
            In this exercise, you will create the DaoJones bean to access Task documents.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            After completion, you are able to access the database to read and write Task documents.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="tasks/3_CreateTaskBean.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Create Task" skip="false">
         <intro>
            In this step, you will write some lines of code to create a simple task item.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            Congratulations, you have now created a document in the database.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="tasks/4_CreateTask.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Search for Task" skip="false">
         <intro>
            The next exercise handles the DaoJones query language.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            Thats all! Thank you!
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="tasks/5_SearchTask.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
   </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet>
